<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sci5</string>
    <string name="title_1">1 - Question</string>
    <string name="title_2">2 - Research</string>
    <string name="title_3">3 - Hypothesis</string>
    <string name="title_4">4 - Experiment</string>
    <string name="title_5">5 - Conclusion</string>
    <string name="content_1">The first step is to make observations. \n\n
        Which phenomena can you observe in your field of interest? \n\n
        Know how to ask a question about what you observe is as much important as making the
        observation itself. \n\n
        How, What, When, Who, Which, Why, or Where?\n\n
        The only requirement for this step is your curiosity.\n\n
        Ex: Which car body shape reduces air resistance most effectively?
  </string>
    <string name="content_2">Before you start doing things you should know what other people already
        have done.\n\n
        This step is important so you can expand your knowledge on the subject. \n\n
        You can learn from the work of others and avoid repeating the same mistakes.\n\n
        The web is your best ally here.\n\n
        Google Scholar is a excellent place to begin with.
    </string>
    <string name="content_3">Now that you have made observations, asked yourself a question and
        studied enough on the subject, it is time to put together what you know and formulate a
        hypothesis. \n\n
        To formulate a hypothesis you should use your intuition and deductive reasoning.
        A hypothesis is  a \"if...then\" statement.\n\n
        There are two requirements to be met: the hypothesis should be testable and falsifiable.\n\n
        It needs to be possible to run a experiment that allow to test the validity of the statement
        and to show that the ideia is not true, if that is the case.\n\n
        Ex: If a car\'s body profile is related to the amount of air resistance it produces,
        then a car designed like the body of a bird will be more aerodynamic and reduce air resistance
        more than a car designed like a box.
    </string>
    <string name="content_4">A well designed experiment should test a specific hypothesis and must
        be controlled.\n\n
        The independent variable is the one that\'s controlled and manipulated by the experimenter,
        while the dependent variable is not. \n\n
        As the independent variable is manipulated, the dependent variable is measured for variation.\n\n
        Ex: the independent variable is the shape of the car\'s body. The dependent variable could
        be speed, gas mileage or a direct measure of the amount of air pressure exerted on the car.
    </string>
    <string name="content_5">As soon as your experiments are concluded, should have gathered an amount
    of qualitative and quantitative data. What conclusions can you draw from it?\n\n
    Now it is time to analyze this data in search for the evidence to support or reject your hypothesis. \n\n
    Have you proved your hypothesis and answered your question ? Congratulations! Now you can show
    your work and results to other scientists.  \n\n
    Have you found that your hypothesis is not supported by evidence ? Do not worry! That is the way
    that science works. Maybe you can rethink on your experiments or reformulate your hypothesis.
    Science is a iterative process, you should repeat your steps until you have a desired result.
    </string>



</resources>
